{
    "id": "2550df68152140aab0a742ab5db4917c",
    "title": "Reported Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He said that he ...................... a toothache.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has got",
                "had got",
                "have got"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e85c02ca57374c518ede3e7262a5beb4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Manu said that he .................... very busy then.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a279b5c42ef144879d85bb3c09052c13"
        },
        {
            "question": "She told us ....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that hurry up",
                "to hurry up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8ac4130da8a4e6c931479721626c810"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked her ........................ him a cup of water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "giving",
                "to give"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7d3bc0a2e3e34e26b0c318517c22f7bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ...................... going to college.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc35eaef897d4be5a7b477331d3e1a9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju said that Gautam ..................... to go the following day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have",
                "would have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "354355c4ba1c49a0817d10fd52247f82"
        },
        {
            "question": "Geetha says that her father ...................... an Engineer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4d5218021b5432cb69e34e299994ad5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ........................ the physical test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has passed",
                "passed",
                "had passed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2589cab12e16478dbdd1abb7e7ba5cc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She told me that I .................. her only friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "have been",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4adeb8b1e98546749a2e80b54402eb99"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me that he .................... me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loves",
                "is loving",
                "loved"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "531d2c3042df4895a05837e3f38c4e75"
        },
        {
            "question": "James asked Mary .........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where was she going",
                "where she was going",
                "where has she gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e41d75f142184dfc897b1c545e9a7303"
        }
    ]
}